question_data = {
        "Identify": [
            {
                "question_text": "Which of these is not a component of STEM?",
                "correct_answer": " Mathematics, Technology, Science, Engineering",
                "wrong_answers": [ "Electronics"]
            },

            {
                "question_text": "What is engineering?",
                "correct_answer": "The process of using science and mathematics to simplify life",
                "wrong_answers": ["The process of making machines and computers"]
            },

            {
                "question_text": " How do you know if your technology is safe and good for consumption?",
                "correct_answer": "By testing the prototypes",
                "wrong_answers": ["By improving it", "By selling it for a low price"]
            },

            {
                "question_text": "What is a prototype?",
                "correct_answer": "The first samples of a technology that someone makes ",
                "wrong_answers": ["The final technology that someone makes", "a kind of computer software"]
            },
            {
                "question_text": "Why did we conduct the energy survey?" ,
                "correct_answer": "To find out if lack of electricity is a serious problem " ,
                "wrong_answers": ["To find out if we have other sources of energy " ]
            },
            {
                "question_text": "What are technologies?" ,
                "correct_answer": "They all simplify life or solve a problem" ,
                "wrong_answers": ["They all use electricity to work" ]
            },
            {
                "question_text": "What are technologies?" ,
                "correct_answer": "To find out if lack of electricity is a serious problem " ,
                "wrong_answers": ["To find out if we have other sources of energy " ]
            },

        ],
        "Create": [

            {
                "question_text": "How will you get anthocyanin dye?" ,
                "correct_answer": "Mixing hibiscus flowers in little warm water" ,
                "wrong_answers": ["Mixing hibiscus flowers in little ethanol"]
            },
            {
                "question_text": "Which of these is not necessary to create solar cells?" ,
                "correct_answer": " Chlorophyll" ,
                "wrong_answers": ["Titanium dioxide", "Anthocyanin", "Iodine"]
            },
            {
                "question_text": "The N type material should be on which material?" ,
                "correct_answer": "The metal strip" ,
                "wrong_answers": ["The paper "]
            },
            {
                "question_text": "What is the iodine solution used for in a dye-sensitized solar cell?" ,
                "correct_answer": "Electrolyte" ,
                "wrong_answers": ["Photocatalyst", "Semiconductor"]
            },
            {
                "question_text": "What is the anthocyanin dye used for in a dye-sensitized solar cell?  " ,
                "correct_answer": "Photocatalyst",
                "wrong_answers": ["Electrolyte", "Semiconductor"]
            },
        ],
        "Brainstorm": [

            {
                "question_text": "How will you get anthocyanin dye?" ,
                "correct_answer": "Mixing hibiscus flowers in little warm water" ,
                "wrong_answers": ["Mixing hibiscus flowers in little ethanol"]
            },
            {
                "question_text": "Which of these is not necessary to create solar cells?" ,
                "correct_answer": " Chlorophyll" ,
                "wrong_answers": ["Titanium dioxide", "Anthocyanin", "Iodine"]
            },
            {
                "question_text": "The N type material should be on which material?" ,
                "correct_answer": "The metal strip" ,
                "wrong_answers": ["The paper "]
            },
            {
                "question_text": "What is the iodine solution used for in a dye-sensitized solar cell?" ,
                "correct_answer": "Electrolyte" ,
                "wrong_answers": ["Photocatalyst", "Semiconductor"]
            },
            {
                "question_text": "What is the anthocyanin dye used for in a dye-sensitized solar cell?  " ,
                "correct_answer": "Photocatalyst",
                "wrong_answers": ["Electrolyte", "Semiconductor"]
            },
        ],


    }

